<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SVR</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">HomeActivity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">S.V.R</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Welcome Guest</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">S.V.R Public School</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_zoom">View</string>

    <string name="school_desc">To achieve the aims and objectives of a school, it is essential that a disciplined approach is adopted to all levels. We have taken great care to strengthen the discipline in the school which actually is a reflection of its soul and it assures a wholesome growth of students.\n\n Our approach to learning process involves some important and contemporary methods, learning takes place through a variety of student-driven activities, Projects, Workshops and Seminars by eminent personalities.\n\n Ours is a school , Which is vibrant in every sense of the word . There are several activities and the students experience situations outside the classroom , which emulate life . Students are happy and enjoy coming to school . Their opinions matter and they have an integral part to play in their own education .</string>
    <string name="hostel_rules">Sed ut perspiciatis unde omnis iste natus error sit voluptatem accUKntium doloremque laudantium, totam rem aperiam, eaque ipsa quae ab illo inventore veritatis et quasi architecto beatae vitae dicta sunt explicabo. Nemo enim ipsam voluptatem quia voluptas sit aspernatur aut odit aut fugit.\n\nConsectetur, adipisci velit, sed quia non numquam eius modi tempora incidunt ut labore et dolore magnam aliquam quaerat voluptatem. Ut enim ad minima veniam, quis nostrum exercitationem ullam corporis suscipit laboriosam, nisi ut aliquid ex ea commodi consequatur.</string>
    <string name="medical_facility">Sed ut perspiciatis unde omnis iste natus error sit voluptatem accUKntium doloremque laudantium, totam rem aperiam, eaque ipsa quae ab illo inventore veritatis et quasi architecto beatae vitae dicta sunt explicabo. Nemo enim ipsam voluptatem quia voluptas sit aspernatur aut odit aut fugit.\n\nConsectetur, adipisci velit, sed quia non numquam eius modi tempora incidunt ut labore et dolore magnam aliquam quaerat voluptatem. Ut enim ad minima veniam, quis nostrum exercitationem ullam corporis suscipit laboriosam, nisi ut aliquid ex ea commodi consequatur.</string>
    <string name="hostel_facility">Sed ut perspiciatis unde omnis iste natus error sit voluptatem accUKntium doloremque laudantium, totam rem aperiam, eaque ipsa quae ab illo inventore veritatis et quasi architecto beatae vitae dicta sunt explicabo. Nemo enim ipsam voluptatem quia voluptas sit aspernatur aut odit aut fugit.\n\nConsectetur, adipisci velit, sed quia non numquam eius modi tempora incidunt ut labore et dolore magnam aliquam quaerat voluptatem. Ut enim ad minima veniam, quis nostrum exercitationem ullam corporis suscipit laboriosam, nisi ut aliquid ex ea commodi consequatur.</string>
    <string name="well_maintained_school">Sed ut perspiciatis unde omnis iste natus error sit voluptatem accUKntium doloremque laudantium, totam rem aperiam, eaque ipsa quae ab illo inventore veritatis et quasi architecto beatae vitae dicta sunt explicabo. Nemo enim ipsam voluptatem quia voluptas sit aspernatur aut odit aut fugit.\n\nConsectetur, adipisci velit, sed quia non numquam eius modi tempora incidunt ut labore et dolore magnam aliquam quaerat voluptatem. Ut enim ad minima veniam, quis nostrum exercitationem ullam corporis suscipit laboriosam, nisi ut aliquid ex ea commodi consequatur.</string>
    <string name="recreation">Sed ut perspiciatis unde omnis iste natus error sit voluptatem accUKntium doloremque laudantium, totam rem aperiam, eaque ipsa quae ab illo inventore veritatis et quasi architecto beatae vitae dicta sunt explicabo. Nemo enim ipsam voluptatem quia voluptas sit aspernatur aut odit aut fugit.\n\nConsectetur, adipisci velit, sed quia non numquam eius modi tempora incidunt ut labore et dolore magnam aliquam quaerat voluptatem. Ut enim ad minima veniam, quis nostrum exercitationem ullam corporis suscipit laboriosam, nisi ut aliquid ex ea commodi consequatur.</string>

    <string name="sports">We have adequate facilities of playgrounds and other instructions for games and sports. Provisions for football, cricket, volleyball and basketball have been availed to the students.\n\nStudents are also trained and promoted to take part in the tournaments organized by the govt and non-govt organizations..</string>
    <string name="library">A well furnished library accomplished with very near to 1,000  magazines , daily news paper and Books on various subjects and editions useful for the students in both school studies and extra knowledge is available.\n\n Students are encouraged to make maximum use of the library facility.</string>
    <string name="transport_facility">Bus facility is available for the students coming from remote areas on payment of certain charge fixed by the school authority. A detailed information regarding that can be availed from the counter persons. Charge vary with the length of route. \n\nThis charge is subject to change as or when required.</string>
    <string name="computer_lab">Beginning from Class LKG onwards, Computer Education is an integral part of the school curriculum. The students are trained in basic skills and techniques of Computer.Separate labs are available for Junior and senior students with specialized softwares and packages for each and every subject.\n\n It is further aided by Internet connections, which can be used under the proper guidance of instructors.</string>
    <string name="smart_classes">There are a few computers presently but the management is trying to enhance the number of computer according to requirement and to link the Lab. With internet and other possible modern facilities in due course to know the changes and development in the world day-to-day. It is running by a highly educated computer teacher.</string>


    <string name="discpline">The school has an own disciplinary chore but it is not much different from common conduct. Students are better educated putting a serve of self discipline and self respect. Placing trust in their intrinsic ability. Boys with a leadership aptitude are given event management opportunities.</string>
    <string name="parent_role">The first and foremost what we expect from the guardians is their faith on us. In order the attain the high academic standard as well as the ideals and aims of the institute, a full co operation of the parents and guardians is essential. Parents are requested to keep an eye on their wards so that the ideals, as stated in the foregoing pages are followed by the students when they go home. Early rising, good manners and gentlemanly behavior, truthfulness and cleanliness should be observed with at home. Boys should not be allowed to see Cinema and TV shows accept those that are appropriate for them. The school cannot rise to perfection, unless the guardians have faith in the educational ideals of the institute and unless a full co operation is received from them.\n\nGuardians or parents may visit the school periodically to meet the concerned  class teacher to take a view on his/her wards progress in academic and other behavioral grounds.</string>

    <string name="clothing_items">Sed ut perspiciatis unde omnis iste natus error sit voluptatem accUKntium doloremque laudantium, totam rem aperiam, eaque ipsa quae ab illo inventore veritatis et quasi architecto beatae vitae dicta sunt explicabo. Nemo enim ipsam voluptatem quia voluptas sit aspernatur aut odit aut fugit.\n\nConsectetur, adipisci velit, sed quia non numquam eius modi tempora incidunt ut labore et dolore magnam aliquam quaerat voluptatem. Ut enim ad minima veniam, quis nostrum exercitationem ullam corporis suscipit laboriosam, nisi ut aliquid ex ea commodi consequatur.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>

    <string name="school_desc_short">The school has its own best hostel facility for students. Parents/ Guardian desirous to admitting their children in the hostel will have to apply in the hostel application  from separately. The student should be medically fit and should not have any physical deficiency/ shortcoming which may come in the day of his/ her participation in all school activities. A well balanced healthy and nourishing diet is ensured besides the three main meals the child gets MILK in the morning and seasonal FRUITS/ SNACKS in the recess.</string>

    <string name="preferences">svrpublic</string>

    <string name="admission">ADMISSION IS GOING ON 2020-21!!!                              ADMISSION IS GOING ON 2020-21!!! </string>
</resources>
